Connecticut State Labor Council, AFL-CIO Records 1989.0080
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series IV: Administrative Records, undated, 1925-1991
  - Subseries N: Committee on Political Education [COPE], undated, 1947-1980
    - Section 5: Voter Information
      - Town and city election data, 1980 (Box 41:, Folder 1831-1832)
    - Section 6: Voter Registration
      - Voter registration, 1958-1970 (Box 41:, Folder 1833-1845)
      - Budget, 1965-1980 (Box 41:, Folder 1846-1858)
      - Contributions, 1958-1967 (Box 42:, Folder 1859-1871)
      - Publications, COPE memorandum, 1956-1957 (Box 42:, Folder 1872)
      - Democratic Party
        - CT State Central Committee, 1972-1976 (Box 42:, Folder 1873-1878)
        - National Committee, 1972-1975 (Box 43:, Folder 1879-1888)
      - Political memorandum from COPE, 1956-1957 (Box 43:, Folder 1889)
      - CT State Labor Council, correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 43:, Folder 1890-1891)
  - Subseries O: Education, undated, 1953-1981
    - Director of Education, Ruth Greenberg, 1960 (Box 43:, Folder 1892-1893)
    - Economic, 1966 (Box 43:, Folder 1894)
    - Legislation, 1967 (Box 43:, Folder 1895)
    - Library Services, 1966-1967 (Box 43:, Folder 1896)
      - Materials request, 1965-1966 (Box 43:, Folder 1897)
      - Miscellaneous, 1962-1967 (Box 43:, Folder 1898)
      - Publication, 1962-1966 (Box 43:, Folder 1899)
      - Scholarship Information, 1963-1965 (Box 43:, Folder 1900)
      - Student loans, 1960 (Box 43:, Folder 1901)
    - University of Connecticut
      - Labor Advisory Committee, 1966 (Box 43:, Folder 1902)
      - Labor Education Center, 1964-1965 (Box 43:, Folder 1903)
    - Vocational, 1966-1967 (Box 43:, Folder 1904)
    - Bridgeport Conference on school dropouts, 1961 (Box 43:, Folder 1905)
    - Books and materials program, undated (Box 44:, Folder 1906)
    - Conference for Educational Committees, 1961 (Box 44:, Folder 1907)
    - CT Educational Television, 1962 (Box 44:, Folder 1908)
    - General, Ruth Greenberg, 1959-1962 (Box 44:, Folder 1909)
    - GHLC, economic aid, Fall Conference, 1962 (Box 44:, Folder 1910)
    - HFTD, Religion-Labor Project, 1960-1962 (Box 44:, Folder 1911)
    - Labor, management and economic security—talks, 1958 (Box 44:, Folder 1912)
    - Labor Education courses, 1961 (Box 44:, Folder 1913)
    - Labor Education programs, 1961 (Box 44:, Folder 1914)
    - Loyalty oath data, 1953 (Box 44:, Folder 1915)
    - Materials requests, 1962 (Box 44:, Folder 1916)
    - National Institute of Labor Education, 1961 (Box 44:, Folder 1917)
    - National Library Week, 1962 (Box 44:, Folder 1918)
    - NAACP, 1958-1962 (Box 44:, Folder 1919)
    - Other Departments—Greenberg, CT, 1962 (Box 44:, Folder 1920-1921)
    - Religion and Labor Council of America, 1962 (Box 44:, Folder 1922)
    - Resource units on Labor, secondary school students and teachers, undated (Box 44:, Folder 1923)
    - State Federations of Labor—Greenberg, 1962 (Box 44:, Folder 1924)
    - CSLC Summer school, 1962-1975 (Box 44:, Folder 1925-1928)
    - Summer school, 1980 (Box 44:, Folder 1929)
    - TalkBack, community services, 1975 (Box 44:, Folder 1930)
    - University of Connecticut, 1962 (Box 44:, Folder 1931)
      - Labor Education Center, 1962-1970 (Box 44:, Folder 1932-1934)
      - Annual reports, 1978-1981 (Box 44:, Folder 1935-1936)
      - Labor-Management Institute, 1960-1962 (Box 44:, Folder 1937)
    - Trade Union Courier, 1954-1958 (Box 44:, Folder 1938-1939)
    - Unemployment, 1953-1960 (Box 44:, Folder 1940)
    - UAW, “News”, 1962 (Box 44:, Folder 1941)
    - WHNC stations, CT Service Council, 1962 (Box 44:, Folder 1942)
    - Community Services, 1973-1977 (Box 44:, Folder 1943-1946)
    - Human Resource Development Institute, Employment and Training Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 44:, Folder 1947-1952)
    - William St. Onge Scholarship, 1965-1972 (Box 44:, Folder 1953)
  - Subseries P: Health and Welfare, undated, 1952-1982
    - AFL-CIO Department of Urban and Housing, undated (Box 45:, Folder 1971)
    - Blue Cross, 1961 (Box 45:, Folder 1972-1973)
    - Bridgeport, undated (Box 132:, Folder 3788-3790)
    - Community services: employment and training, 1973-1977 (Box 45:, Folder 1954-1958)
    - Hartford, undated (Box 132:, Folder 3786)
    - Human Resources Development Institute, 1978-1981 (Box 45:, Folder 1959-1965)
    - Legislation, 1961 (Box 45:, Folder 1966)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 45:, Folder 1967)
    - New England Congressional Caucus, 1978-1979 (Box 45:, Folder 1968)
    - New England Solar Energy Center, 1978-1979 (Box 45:, Folder 1969)
    - OSHA, 1977-1979 (Box 45:, Folder 1970)
    - University of Connecticut
      - Connecticut, 1960 (Box 45:, Folder 1974)
      - Fair Housing Practices, 1961 (Box 45:, Folder 1975)
    - New Haven
      - City Plan Commission, 1962 (Box 45:, Folder 1976)
      - Custodians and Engineers Retirement Fund, 1959 (Box 45:, Folder 1977)
      - Family Services of, Inc., 1959 (Box 45:, Folder 1978)
      - Housing Department, 1959 (Box 45:, Folder 1979)
      - Council of Social Agencies, 1961 (Box 45:, Folder 1980)
      - Urban League, 1962 (Box 45:, Folder 1981)
      - Housing laws, 1962 (Box 45:, Folder 1982)
      - Human Relations Council, 1962 (Box 45:, Folder 1983)
      - Police Department annual report, Centennial issues, 1961 (Box 45:, Folder 1984)
      - Seniors, 1960-1961 (Box 45:, Folder 1985)
      - Nursing Homes: Special Committee on Aging U.S. Senate, undated (Box 45:, Folder 1986)
      - Substandard housing, 1952-1958 (Box 45:, Folder 1987)
      - Welfare and Pension plan Disclosure Act, amended, 1962 (Box 45:, Folder 1988)
      - Workers Health Institute, 1980-1982 (Box 45:, Folder 1989)
    - New Haven, undated (Box 132:, Folder 3787)
    - United Labor Agency, 1984 (Box 132:, Folder 3785)
  - Subseries Q: Testimonials and Memorials, undated, 1959-1979
    - O'Brien-Googel, 1959 (Box 45:, Folder 1990)
    - Msgr. Donnelly, 1959 (Box 45:, Folder 1991)
    - Kowalski, undated (Box 45:, Folder 1992)
    - Sviridoff, 1962 (Box 45:, Folder 1993)
    - Bishop Donnell fund, 1965 (Box 45:, Folder 1994)
    - McAuliffe, 1966-1969 (Box 45:, Folder 1995-1996)
    - John Glenn, 1976 (Box 45:, Folder 1997)
    - Frank “Chuck” Avalone, 1977 (Box 45:, Folder 1998)
    - Peter Reilly, 1979 (Box 45:, Folder 1999)
    - Governor's ball, 1979 (Box 45:, Folder 2000)
  - Subseries R: National and State Issues, 1986
    - CT AFL-CIO communications with US Congressmen, 1986 (Box 174)
    - National Labor Relations Act Violators, 1986 (Box 174)
    - US Department of Labor, 1986 (Box 174)
    - US Legislative Issues, 1986 (Box 174)
    - US Taxes, 1986 (Box 174)
    - International Economy, 1986 (Box 174)
    - CT Democrats, 1986 (Box 174)
    - Governor O'Neill, 1986 (Box 174)
    - Secretary of State, 1986 (Box 174)
    - Department of Health Services, 1986 (Box 174)
    - Commission on Hospitals, 1986 (Box 174)
    - CT Office of Policy and Management, 1986 (Box 174)
    - Permanent Commission on the Status of Women, 1986 (Box 174)
    - Peraro, Commissioner of Labor, 1986 (Box 174)
    - CT Labor Department, 1986 (Box 174)
    - Asbestos, 1986 (Box 174)
    - Amnesty International, 1986 (Box 174)
    - AAUP, 1986 (Box 174)
    - CT Association for Human Services, 1986 (Box 174)
    - CCAG Ad book, 1986 (Box 174)
    - Coalition of Labor Women, 1986 (Box 174)
    - CT Union of Telephone Workers, 1986 (Box 174)
    - Higher Education correspondence, 1986 (Box 174)
    - Freedom of Information, 1986 (Box 174)
    - Good Jobs Campaign, 1986 (Box 174)
    - Naugatuck Valley Project, 1986 (Box 174)
    - Public Broadcasting, 1986 (Box 174)
    - Unemployment Compensation, 1986 (Box 174)
    - United Auto Workers Activity, 1986 (Box 174)
    - Workers' Compensation, 1986 (Box 174)
    - Collapse of L'Ambience Plaza, 1987 (Box 175)
    - Pratt & Whitney; UTC and IAMAW negotiations, 1985 (Box 175)
  - Subseries S: Connecticut AFL-CIO, undated
    - COPE, undated (Box 181)
    - COPE budget, undated (Box 181)
    - Driscoll, John: President Emeritus, undated (Box 181)
    - Driscoll, John: President Emeritus, undated (Box 203)
    - Executive Board, undated (Box 203)
    - Executive Board, undated (Box 203)
    - Financial data, undated (Box 203)
    - Financial reports, undated (Box 203)
    - Financial Reports, undated (Box 181)
    - Health and Safety Committee, undated (Box 181)
    - Housing Investment Committee, undated (Box 181)
    - Legal Counsel, Norman Zolot, undated (Box 181)
    - Legislative Committee (National), undated (Box 181)
    - Looker, Aleta: Secretary to the President, undated (Box 203)
    - MacFadden, Tammy: Secretary Treasurer, undated (Box 203)
    - News releases, undated (Box 181)
    - News releases, undated (Box 203)
    - News releases, undated (Box 203)
    - Newsletter/newspaper, undated (Box 203)
    - Newspaper, undated (Box 181)
    - Newspaper, undated (Box 203)
    - Olsen, President John W., undated (Box 203)
    - Staff, undated (Box 203)
    - Staff memoranda, undated (Box 181)
    - Strike Assistance, undated (Box 181)
    - Testimony by staff, undated (Box 181)
    - Zolot, Norman: legal counsel, undated (Box 203)
- Series V: Legislative Files, undated, 1949-1989
  - Subseries A: Correspondence, 1970-1980
    - John Driscoll, U.S. Senate, 1970-1980 (Box 46:, Folder 2001-2011)
    - John Driscoll, U.S. House of Representatives, 1971-1980 (Box 46:, Folder 2012-2021)
  - Subseries B: Legislative Committees, 1949-1978
    - Personnel Study Committee: CT as an Employer, 1949 (Box 46:, Folder 2022)
    - Commission to study the problem of revision pertaining to state welfare laws, 1960 (Box 46:, Folder 2023)
    - Labor committee, 1971 (Box 46:, Folder 2024)
    - Legislative committee, 1971 (Box 46:, Folder 2025)
    - National Advisory committee, 1970-1971 (Box 46:, Folder 2026)
    - Committee on structure of state, filer report, 1976 (Box 46:, Folder 2027)
    - Governor's committee on employment of handicapped, 1977 (Box 46:, Folder 2028)
    - Economic review committee, 1977 (Box 47:, Folder 2029)
    - Union Labor Legislative Committee, 1975-1977 (Box 47:, Folder 2030)
    - Wilde Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 47:, Folder 2031)
    - House Committee testimony, 1971-1978 (Box 47:, Folder 2032-2038)
  - Subseries C: Platform proposals, 1960-1974
    - Platforms, 1960-1966 (Box 47:, Folder 2039-2049)
    - CT Democratic state platforms, 1962-1974 (Box 47:, Folder 2050)
  - Subseries D: Legislative Conferences, undated, 1975-1981
    - New England Regional Commission, 1978 (Box 48:, Folder 2051)
    - New England Regional Commission and Economic Advisory Committee, 1975-1980 (Box 48:, Folder 2052-2068)
    - White House Conference on Balanced National Economic Growth and Development, undated
    - 1977 October (Box 48:, Folder 2069-2073)
    - 1977 November (Box 48:, Folder 2074-2076)
    - 1978 February (Box 48:, Folder 2077-2081)
    - Council for Northeast Economic Growth, 1975-1977 (Box 48:, Folder 2082-2089)
    - Northeast Economic Council, 1978-1981 (Box 49:, Folder 2090-2100)
  - Subseries E: General Assembly, undated, 1970-1981
    - Representatives, undated (Box 132:, Folder 3792)
    - Senatorial districts, undated (Box 50:, Folder 2101)
    - Senators, undated (Box 132:, Folder 3791)
    - Legislative bulletins, 1979 (Box 50:, Folder 2102)
    - Copies, undated (Box 50:, Folder 2103-2104)
    - General Assembly, special session, 1979 (Box 50:, Folder 2105)
    - Legislative correspondence, 1979 (Box 50:, Folder 2106)
    - Legislative files
      - Labor committee, 1979 (Box 50:, Folder 2107)
      - Summary, scorecard, status report, 1980 (Box 50:, Folder 2108)
      - House bill listing, 1981 (Box 50:, Folder 2109)
    - Duplicates of Box 50, undated (Box 51:, Folder 2110-2119)
    - 1980 (Box 132:, Folder 3820)
    - 1982 (Box 132:, Folder 3821-3824)
    - 1983 (Box 132:, Folder 3825-3827)
    - 1984 (Box 132:, Folder 3828)
    - 1985 (Box 132:, Folder 3829-3832)
  - Subseries F: Gubernatorial Files, undated, 1972-1980
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 51)
      - Thomas Meskill, 1972-1973 (Box 51:, Folder 2120-2121)
      - Ella T. Grasso, 1974-1980 (Box 51:, Folder 2122-2126)
    - Governor's Blue Ribbon Commission on Education, 1981 (Box 51:, Folder 2127)
    - Coalition of Northeast Governors (CONEG), undated (Box 52)
      - Conference, 1976 (Box 52:, Folder 2128-2129)
      - Correspondence and notes, 1978-1979 (Box 52:, Folder 2130-2132)
  - Subseries G: Connecticut Government Departments, 1968-1978
    - Attorney General, 1971-1977 (Box 53:, Folder 2133)
    - Aging, 1969-1975 (Box 53:, Folder 2134)
    - Arts, 1971 (Box 53:, Folder 2135)
    - Banking, 1977 (Box 53:, Folder 2136)
    - Children and Youth Services, 1972-1975 (Box 53:, Folder 2137)
    - Commerce, 1973-1977 (Box 53:, Folder 2138-2139)
    - Commerce, Committee of Concern for CT jobs, 1974-1976 (Box 53:, Folder 2140)
    - Community Affairs, 1971-1977 (Box 53:, Folder 2141)
    - Crime and corrections, 1971-1972 (Box 53:, Folder 2142)
    - Environmental Protection, 1972-1978 (Box 53:, Folder 2143)
    - Human Services, 1972-1976 (Box 53:, Folder 2144)
    - Insurance, 1974-1977 (Box 53:, Folder 2145)
    - Labor Commissioner, 1975-1977 (Box 53:, Folder 2146)
    - Personnel, 1978 (Box 54:, Folder 2147)
    - Secretary of State, 1968-1977 (Box 54:, Folder 2148)
  - Subseries H: Atomic Energy, undated, 1952-1988
    - Section 1: Correspondence, 1956-1960
      - Andrew Biemiller, 1956 (Box 54:, Folder 2149)
      - Henry H. Marx, 1956 (Box 54:, Folder 2150-2151)
      - Linus Pauling, 1960 (Box 54:, Folder 2152)
      - William Schnitzler, 1957 (Box 54:, Folder 2153)
      - Hugh Ward, 1956 (Box 54:, Folder 2154)
    - Section 2: AFL-CIO Conference on Atomic Energy, undated, 1957
      - Workmen's Compensation, 1957 (Box 54:, Folder 2155)
      - Atomic energy development, undated (Box 54:, Folder 2156)
      - Radiation hazards, undated (Box 54:, Folder 2157)
      - Labor's stake in atomic energy, undated (Box 54:, Folder 2158)
      - Remarks by Walter Reuther, 1957 (Box 54:, Folder 2159)
    - Section 3: General subject file, undated, 1952-1988
      - American Nuclear Society, 1957 (Box 54:, Folder 2160)
      - Atomic Energy Bill, 1956 (Box 54:, Folder 2161)
      - Atomic energy development plan for NY State, 1959 (Box 54:, Folder 2162)
      - CT nuclear development, 1956-1961 (Box 54:, Folder 2163)
      - Federal and legal aspects of nuclear energy, 1957 (Box 54:, Folder 2164)
      - Forand Bill, 1958 (Box 54:, Folder 2165)
      - Health and safety, labor memorandum, undated (Box 54:, Folder 2166)
      - Implications of the Nuclear Age on high school curricula, 1957 (Box 54:, Folder 2167)
      - Institute for Atomics, 1956 (Box 54:, Folder 2168)
      - International Association of Accident Boards and Commissions, 1956 (Box 54:, Folder 2169)
      - Legislative frontiers of atomic energy, 1957 (Box 54:, Folder 2170)
      - Northeast nuclear advocate, 1977 (Box 54:, Folder 2171)
      - Radiation sources and materials, CT Dept. of Health, 1952-1988 (Box 54:, Folder 2172)
      - Report of Labor Seminar: panel on the impact of peaceful uses of atomic energy, 1955 (Box 54:, Folder 2173)
      - Pamphlet material, 1956 (Box 54:, Folder 2174)
      - Uses of radiation in CT, 1957 (Box 54:, Folder 2175)
      - U.S. Atomic Energy Commission, 1957-1960 (Box 54:, Folder 2176-2177)
      - U.S. Atomic Energy Commission: facts, 1957 (Box 54:, Folder 2178)
      - U.S. Department of Commerce: radiation protection standards, 1956 (Box 54:, Folder 2179)
  - Subseries I: Education, 1959-1977
    - Correspondence, 1970-1977 (Box 54:, Folder 2180-2184)
    - CT Humanities Council, 1970-1977 (Box 55:, Folder 2185)
    - Educational Directory of CT, 1959-1967 (Box 55:, Folder 2186)
    - Labor and vocational education, 1963-1965 (Box 55:, Folder 2187)
    - UConn Labor Education Center, 1970-1977 (Box 55:, Folder 2188-2193)
  - Subseries J: Health and Welfare, undated, 1956-1979
    - Correspondence, 1967-1971 (Box 55:, Folder 2194-2197)
    - America's health needs, 1963 (Box 55:, Folder 2198)
    - Medical care for the aged, 1961 (Box 55:, Folder 2199)
    - National Council for Senior Citizens, Medicare Supplement Plan, undated (Box 55:, Folder 2200)
    - National Health Insurance, 1956 (Box 55:, Folder 2201)
    - OSHA
      - General, 1970-1972 (Box 55:, Folder 2202)
      - Administration, 1976-1977 (Box 55:, Folder 2203)
      - House Bill 7280, 1977 (Box 55:, Folder 2204)
      - Industry Standards, 1977 (Box 55:, Folder 2205)
      - Senate voting record, 1976 (Box 55:, Folder 2206)
      - UConn Labor Center, undated (Box 55:, Folder 2207)
    - Senior Intern program, 1974-1975 (Box 55:, Folder 2208)
    - Welfare, 1979 (Box 55:, Folder 2209)
  - Subseries K: Taxation, 1961-1981
    - General, 1961-1963 (Box 56:, Folder 2210-2212)
    - CT Conference of municipalities, 1976-1979 (Box 56:, Folder 2213)
    - Council of Employment and Fair Taxation, 1976-1981 (Box 56:, Folder 2214-2216)
    - Legislative session tax material, 1981 (Box 56:, Folder 2217)
    - State revenue tax force, 1969-1971 (Box 56:, Folder 2218-2222)
  - Subseries L: United Labor Agency, undated, 1979-1980
    - Section 1: Correspondence file, 1979-1980
      - General, 1979-1980 (Box 57:, Folder 2223-2236)
    - Section 2: Subject file, undated, 1979-1980
      - A, 1980 (Box 57:, Folder 2237)
      - Board of Director's meeting—minutes, reports, undated (Box 57:, Folder 2238)
      - CT United Labor community service—minutes and reports, undated (Box 57:, Folder 2239)
        - Correspondence with United Way (Box 57:, Folder 2240)
        - Correspondence with unions, undated (Box 57:, Folder 2241)
        - General Correspondence, undated (Box 57:, Folder 2242)
        - By-laws, constitution, 1979-1980 (Box 57:, Folder 2243)
      - United Labor Committee: strike pay, 1980 (Box 57:, Folder 2244)
      - United Way boycott: press clippings, 1980 (Box 57:, Folder 2245)
      - United Way responses, 1980 (Box 57:, Folder 2246)
  - Subseries M: Subject Files, undated, 1952-1991
    - AFL-CIO candidate questionnaire, 1980 (Box 57:, Folder 2247)
    - AFL-CIO Summer school, 1988 (Box 191)
    - American Family Celebration, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Analysis of political vulnerability of congressmen, 1977 (Box 57:, Folder 2248)
    - Anti-Apartheid Committee, undated (Box 143)
    - Anti-inflation policies, 1977-1978 (Box 57:, Folder 2249)
    - Appropriations Committee, 1987 (Box 182)
    - Bills—House and Senate (CT), 1979-1981 (Box 57:, Folder 2250-2254)
    - Ban the can, 1975-1977 (Box 57:, Folder 2255)
    - Banks, 1971 (Box 57:, Folder 2256)
    - Banking Committee, 1985 (Box 182)
    - Campaign financing, undated (Box 143)
    - Campaign letters, 1980 (Box 57:, Folder 2257)
    - CETA, application for funding, 1979 (Box 57:, Folder 2258)
    - Citizens' Coalition for current federal issues, 1977 (Box 57:, Folder 2259)
    - City and town development act, 1979 (Box 57:, Folder 2260)
    - Civil Action #15105, U.S. District Court, 1972 (Box 57:, Folder 2261)
    - Collective bargaining for state employees, 1975 (Box 7:, Folder 2262)
    - Collective bargaining rights for municipal supervisors, 1978 (Box 58:, Folder 2263)
    - Colorado State Labor Council, 1972 (Box 58:, Folder 2265)
    - Concerned Seniors for Better Government, 1974-1981 (Box 58:, Folder 2266-2272)
    - Congressional districts, undated (Box 143)
      - 1st, undated (Box 143)
      - 1st, undated (Box 196)
      - 2nd, undated (Box 143)
      - 2nd, undated (Box 196)
      - 3rd, undated (Box 143)
      - 3rd, undated (Box 196)
      - 4th, undated (Box 196)
      - 5th, undated (Box 143)
      - 5th, undated (Box 196)
      - 6th, undated (Box 143)
      - 6th, undated (Box 196)
    - Connecticut, undated (Box 143)
    - Connecticut celebration, undated (Box 143)
    - Connecticut colleges, 1971-1976 (Box 58:, Folder 2264)
    - COPE
      - General, 1986-1987 (Box 182)
      - Committee, 1986 (Box 182)
      - Check off, undated (Box 182)
      - Deductions, undated (Box 182)
      - Flyers, undated (Box 182)
      - Scorecard, undated (Box 182)
      - Questionnaire, undated (Box 182)
    - COPE work, undated (Box 143)
    - Corrections, Department of, undated (Box 203)
    - Correspondence, COPE, undated (Box 143)
    - Council of Social Agencies, 1967 (Box 58:, Folder 2277)
    - CSFT on taxes, undated (Box 143)
    - CT Council of Economic Advisors, 1972-1980 (Box 58:, Folder 2273-2276)
    - Davis, undated (Box 143)
    - Dickey-Lincoln Project, 1969 (Box 58:, Folder 2278)
    - DiNordi, undated (Box 143)
    - Diocesan Bureau of Social Services, New Haven, 1959 (Box 58:, Folder 2279)
    - Directory of CT manufacturing establishments, 1962 (Box 58:, Folder 2280)
    - Dodd, Christopher, undated (Box 143)
    - Economic Summit, 1991 (Box 203)
    - Education Committee, undated (Box 143)
    - Education Committee, 1987 (Box 182)
    - Education, Department of, undated (Box 203)
    - Egan, John file, 1979-1982 (Box 58:, Folder 2281)
    - Election statistics, 1962 (Box 59:, Folder 2282)
    - Employment, 1972-1975 (Box 59:, Folder 2283)
    - Employment Security Division, 1987 (Box 182)
    - Ethics Commission, undated (Box 203)
    - Fair housing practices ordinance, 1961-1962 (Box 59:, Folder 2284)
    - Federal election campaign amendments, 1976 (Box 59:, Folder 2285)
    - Federal legislative meeting, 1980 (Box 182:, Folder 2286)
    - General Assembly, 1986 (Box 182)
    - General trade regulations, 1978 (Box 59:, Folder 2287)
    - House of Representatives, 1985, 1988; (2 fl) (Box 182)
    - Human Services Coalition, undated (Box 143)
    - Initiative proposal, state-wide referendum, 1978 (Box 59:, Folder 2288)
    - International affairs training, Meany Center, 1989 (Box 191)
    - I-84 data, 1971-1972 (Box 59:, Folder 2289)
    - J.P. Stevens boycott, 1978-1980 (Box 59:, Folder 2290)
    - Kennedys of Connecticut, undated (Box 59:, Folder 2291)
    - Labor, Connecticut Department of: Commissioner Ronald F. Petronella, undated (Box 203)
    - Labor Day parade, Groton, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Labor Department, 1981 (Box 182)
    - Labor Law reform, undated (Box 59)
      - AFL-CIO memorandum, 1972-1978 (Box 59:, Folder 2292)
      - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 59:, Folder 2293)
      - Pamphlets, 1972-1978 (Box 59:, Folder 2294-2295)
    - Labor-management cooperation, 1971 (Box 59:, Folder 2296)
    - Labor Realty Company of New Haven, 1962 (Box 59:, Folder 2297)
    - Labor Relations, State Board of, 1981-1985; (2 fl) (Box 182)
    - Landrum-Griffen Act, 1960 (Box 59:, Folder 2298)
    - Legislation, 1987 (Box 182)
    - Legislative bulletins, 1991 (Box 203)
    - Legislative Conference, 1985-1987; (6 fl) (Box 182)
    - Legislative Conference, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Legislative Conference, 1989 (Box 191)
    - Legislative Issues—National, undated (Box 193)
    - Legislative session, 1988; (2 fl) (Box 190)
    - Legislative session, undated (Box 203)
    - Legislative Sessions, 1989 (Box 193)
      - Bulletins, undated (Box 193)
      - Parental leave and children, undated (Box 193)
      - Proposed legislation, undated (Box 193)
      - Public Health Committee, undated (Box 193)
      - State legislation, undated (Box 193)
    - Legislature, 1969 (Box 59:, Folder 2299)
    - Legislature: quids and fines, 1974-1977 (Box 59:, Folder 2300)
    - Legislature, House roll call, 1971 (Box 60:, Folder 2301)
    - McLaughlin, James P., 1972 (Box 60:, Folder 2302)
    - Meany, George—memorial mass, 1980 (Box 60:, Folder 2303)
    - Mediation and Arbitration Board, undated (Box 182)
    - Mental Health Department, 1986 (Box 182)